I'm going to be talking about motions that you can be doing in the head.
I'm going to be pressing down and going towards the crown, but I'm also going to alternate it with a little bit of thumb circling going towards the crown.
My fingers over here are tight.
They're pointing towards the ear.
I'm just motioning in circular motions going towards the crown.
This can be done very light.
This can be done very firm, but not hard.
It's great for headaches.
I'm moving everything toward the crown because if there's any type of tension in the forehead area, I'm giving it pathway to move towards the crown.
This doesn't necessarily have to be done with the thumb.
I can do it with all 4 fingers, but in a little more gentler of a motion going towards the crown.
Then give it a glide down.
Always saying hello and goodbye to the head because I'm doing this combing motion with the hair.